geekygadgetworld.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Geeky Gadget World

**GeekyGadgetWorld.Com Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy for **http://GeekyGadgetWorld.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.

At **http://www.GeekyGadgetWorld.Com** , We are extremely concerned about the privacy of each and every visitor of our blog. We hereby want to inform you about the way data about your personal information is received and stored by **http://GeekyGadgetWorld.Com**. We also want you to know how and to what extent these data are being used by us.

**USE OF LOG FILES**

We are using Log Files – Log files are being used by many other sites including us. These files contains information regarding IP address, type of browser used, ISP information, viewed and exit pages, date and time record and the number of clicks to get an idea of the browsing behaviour. These files are used to know what type of content are being liked by our viewers so that we can provide more and more information on that. We also gather demographic information. However we want to make it clear that data like IP address and other such datas are not at all linked to any personal information which can reveal anyone’s identity.

**Browser Cookies**

******http://GeekyGadgetWorld.com** uses cookies for storing information. These information include data about the visitor’s preferences. It also records information about which page any user has visited. It also stores any other information sent by the browser being used for accessing GeekyGadgetWorld.

**Third Party Cookies**

We have different advertising partners with us who may use cookies, web beacons on GeekyGadgetWorld. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These cookies are used by them to serve you the most relevant ad which may be helpful for you. The third-party services has their own way of receiving the data and sending it to your browser automatically. The whole process is fully automatic and include technologies to measure effectiveness of different ads being shown on our sites. These technologies may include cookies, javaScript and even web beacons.

**http://GeekyGadgetWorld.com** does not have access or any type of control check on these technologies served by third-party advertisement agents. We are also in no way using these datas. For further enquiry about their privacy policy you may consult their respective privacy policies. GeekyGadgetWorld privacy policy does not comply to them.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
